https://www.microcomcorp.com/privacy-policy-corporate-responsibility/

Video Gallery
Select PageHomeProducts    New Features        RFID        Touchscreen    Desktop Printers        520 THERMAL DESKTOP PRINTER        438 THERMAL DESKTOP PRINTER        438 THERMAL POSTAL PRINTER        438TC THERMAL DESKTOP PRINTER        485TC THERMAL DESKTOP PRINTER        485T THERMAL DESKTOP PRINTER        360C COLOR LASER TICKET + LABEL PRINTER    Ticket Printers        485TC THERMAL TICKET PRINTER        485T THERMAL TICKET PRINTER        360C COLOR LASER TICKET + LABEL PRINTER        520 THERMAL TICKET PRINTER        540 THERMAL TICKET PRINTER    Kiosk Products        Receipt        Label Ticket + Tag        Wristband    Specialty Products        360C COLOR LASER TICKET + LABEL PRINTER        238B BATTERY POWERED THERMAL PRINTER        238AC THERMAL PRINTER        428L LINERLESS THERMAL PRINTER    Archived ProductsSupport    Manuals    Warranty Information    Technical Support    FAQ’sDownloadsService    Service Plans    RMA RequestSuppliesCustom SolutionsPressAbout    Careers    Contact Us        Contact Us Form        RMA Request        Technical Support RequestVideo Gallery
Privacy Policy & Corporate Responsibility
You are here:Home Privacy Policy & Corporate Responsibility
PRIVACY POLICY
Microcom Corporation collects personal information when you register or contribute online, request information about our products and services, participate in a promotion or online survey, contact us with a question or suggestion, or use our Apps or Services. Depending on the nature of your interaction, we may ask you for information such as your name, phone number, physical address, company related information, email address, credit card information including expiration date and billing address, and product preferences.
The RFID@INTIX App provides a process for Exhibitors to collect Attendee information at events, conferences, and trade shows (the “Services”). The Services include access to Mobile Apps, Branded Event Apps, and website pages on which Services are provided by us (the “Apps”). The Data collected from your name badge is limited to a registration ID and the information visible on the name badge. This information and any exhibitor created notes are later combined with INTIX registration data and provided to INTIX and the appropriate authorized exhibitor.
This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the Services and Apps, whether you are a customer or an end user of the Services. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect through your use of the Apps and any other means by which we may collect information about you.  This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our Apps or use our Services in general, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.  If you permit an exhibitor to scan the RFID Tag on your name badge, that Personal Data will be provided to that exhibitor, who may combine it with additional information and who may use it to direct marketing or sales information to you.
By accessing or using our Apps, using our Services, or contacting us, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to the practices as described in this Privacy Policy. If you are an end user, you acknowledge that we will share the information collected, including personal information, with INTIX for the purpose of providing the Services as agreed to in the INTIX Privacy Policy.
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, and we strive to implement and maintain reasonable, commercially acceptable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information we store, in order to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.
You can request at anytime that we do not share your personal information with such third parties.
Except for email messages related to a direct action by you, such as a password reset request or order confirmation, any email message sent to you by Microcom Corporation offers you the option to be excluded from future email messages. You may request to be removed from our systems at anytime by contacting us at customerservice@microcomcorp.com
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Apps or Services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check our Privacy Policy periodically for updates.
CORPORATE RESPONSIBILITY
Our commitment to delivering quality products is a core value; so too is our commitment to ensuring that we operate our business in an ethical, safe, and environmentally sound manner. Microcom Corporation believes we have a responsibility to:
– Protect the health and safety of our employees and the public by going beyond regulatory obligations;
– Adhere to strict ethical standards and comply with all applicable laws to ensure integrity;
– Promote long-term social and economic development in communities where we operate.
WEEE COMPLIANCE
Waste Electrical and Electronic Equipment (WEEE) is a European Community directive that became European Law in February 2003 and took effect August 13, 2005. Its intent is to reduce the number of electrical and electronic products that end up in the wrong place. The directive sets collection, recovery, and recycling locations for all types of electrical goods sold in the European Union. As of August 13, 2005, electrical equipment sold in Europe, including printers, must be disposed of in accordance with WEEE. According to the directive, only equipment purchased after this date must be recycled. Microcom Corporation has created a recycling program in Europe where Microcom equipment marked with the crossed-out wheelie bin symbol can be returned to the point of sale (or the point where new Microcom equipment is being purchased) at its end of life. Microcom will then arrange for the equipment to be recycled. As the US comes on-line with similar recycling requirements, Microcom is in a position to offer similar locations. Currently, there is no such standard for non-retail products, but if the product is returned to Microcom, we will ensure proper disposal is achieved.
ROHS CERTIFICATION
RoHS Certification Statement for Microcom Corporation Products
Youtube Feed
Facebook Feed
Microcom Corporation:
About to buy a printer? Know the market by reading this Microcom Corporation sponsored white paper.
Click Here
Contact Us
Address:8220 Green Meadows Dr NLewis Center, OH   43035
Phone:
(740) 548-6262
Email: sales@microcomcorp.com
